[{"instructions":"Let's define a new operation +<sub>6</sub>. This operation will give us a way of combining two of the numbers 0, 1, 2, 3, 4, 5 to get another one of them back. To perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result. (That's why the operation is called +<sub>6</sub>.) <br /><br />For example, 3 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 2, because 3 + 5 = 8, and 8 is bigger than 6, so we subtract 6, and 8 - 6 = 2. So 3 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 2.<br /><br />Similarly, 1 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 5, because 1 + 4 = 5, and 5 is less than 6 so we leave it alone. <br /><br />Click \"Continue\" when you're ready to move on.","rt":1345,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":1,"time_elapsed":3738,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Now try one on your own! What is 4 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</su b>, you  start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"15","response_history":["15"],"rt":42207,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":2,"time_elapsed":45948,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that was incorrect. 4 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 3 because 4 + 5 = 9 and 9 - 6 = 3.","rt":6523,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":3,"time_elapsed":52474,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"question":"What is 3 +<sub>6</sub> 2? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"5","response":"11 ","response_history":["11"],"rt":109193,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":4,"time_elapsed":161669,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that was incorrect. 3 +<sub>6</sub> 2 = 5 because 3 + 2 = 5 and 5 is less than 6.","rt":6391,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":5,"time_elapsed":168067,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"5","response_history":["5"],"rt":122302,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":6,"time_elapsed":290373,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that was incorrect. 1 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 0 because 1 + 5 = 6 and 6 - 6 = 0.","rt":2701,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":7,"time_elapsed":293083,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","response_history":["2"],"rt":4349,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":8,"time_elapsed":297434,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 = 2 because 1 + 1 = 2 and 2 is less than 6.","rt":2245,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":9,"time_elapsed":299681,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"question":"What is 3 +<sub>6</sub> 0? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If t he sum i s smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","response_history":["3"],"rt":5679,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":10,"time_elapsed":305362,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 3 +<sub>6</sub> 0 = 3 because 3 + 0 = 3 and 3 is less than 6.","rt":1319,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":11,"time_elapsed":306683,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"question":"What is 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","response_history":["2"],"rt":5057,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":12,"time_elapsed":311744,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 2 because 4 + 4 = 8 and 8 - 6 = 2.","rt":1294,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":13,"time_elapsed":313039,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>6</sub> 3? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"4","response":"2","response_history":["2"],"rt":229521,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":14,"time_elapsed":542563,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that was incorrect. 1 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 4 because 1 + 3 = 4 and 4 is less than 6.","rt":1222,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":15,"time_elapsed":543794,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0. 2-0"},{"question":"What is 4 +<sub>6</sub> 3? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"1","response":"1","response_history":["1"],"rt":3772,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":16,"time_elapsed":547568,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 1 because 4 + 3 = 7 and 7 - 6 = 1.","rt":982,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":17,"time_elapsed":548552,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"question":"What is 0 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"5","response":"5","response_history":["5"],"rt":8262,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":18,"time_elapsed":556815,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 0 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 5 because 0 + 5 = 5 and 5 is less than 6.","rt":910,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":19,"time_elapsed":557726,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"question":"What is 2 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"1","response":"1","response_history":["1"],"rt":3344,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":20,"time_elapsed":561071,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 2 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 1  because  2 + 5 = 7 and 7 - 6 = 1.","rt":966,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":21,"time_elapsed":562038,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"question":"What is 3 +<sub>6</sub> 3? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","response_history":["0"],"rt":3308,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":22,"time_elapsed":565350,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 3 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 0 because 3 + 3 = 6 and 6 - 6 = 0.","rt":935,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":23,"time_elapsed":566286,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>6</sub> 2? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and  then ad d the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","response_history":["3"],"rt":78940,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":24,"time_elapsed":645228,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 1 +<sub>6</sub> 2 = 3 because 1 + 2 = 3 and 3 is less than 6.","rt":919,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":25,"time_elapsed":646156,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"4","response":"4","response_history":["4"],"rt":2748,"trial_type":" question ","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":26,"time_elapsed":648906,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 4 because 5 + 5 = 10 and 10 - 6 = 4.","rt":942,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":27,"time_elapsed":649851,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 4 +<sub>6</sub> 2? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","response_history":["0"],"rt":80651,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":28,"time_elapsed":730503,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 +<sub>6</sub> 2 = 0 because 4 + 2 = 6 and 6 - 6 = 0.","rt":1046,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":29,"time_elapsed":731551,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 0 +<sub>6</sub> 2? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","response_history":["2"],"rt":4662,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":30,"time_elapsed":736214,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 0 +<sub>6</sub> 2 = 2 because 0 + 2 = 2 and 2 is less than 6.","rt":886,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":31,"time_elapsed":737102,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 3 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to g et your  result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","response_history":["2"],"rt":3544,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":32,"time_elapsed":740647,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 3 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 2 because 3 + 5 = 8 and 8 - 6 = 2.","rt":886,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":33,"time_elapsed":741534,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>6</sub> 4? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"5","response":"5","response_history":["5"],"rt":39642,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":34,"time_elapsed":781177,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 1 +<sub>6< /sub> 4  = 5 because 1 + 4 = 5 and 5 is less than 6.","rt":892,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":35,"time_elapsed":782072,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 5 +<sub>6</sub> 1? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","response_history":["0"],"rt":2679,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":36,"time_elapsed":784753,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 5 +<sub>6</sub> 1 = 0 because 5 + 1 = 6 and 6 - 6 = 0.","rt":983,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":37,"time_elapsed":785737,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>6</sub> 0? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with th e first  number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"1","response":"1","response_history":["1"],"rt":4198,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":38,"time_elapsed":789936,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 1 +<sub>6</sub> 0 = 1 because 1 + 0 = 1 and 1 is less than 6.","rt":911,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":39,"time_elapsed":790849,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 5 +<sub>6</sub> 2? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"1","response":"1","response_history":["1"],"rt":19130,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":40,"time_elapsed":809981,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 5 +<sub>6</sub> 2 = 1 because 5 + 2 = 7 and 7 - 6 = 1.","rt":1087,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":41,"time_elapsed":811069,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"instructions":"Now we're going to discuss a couple special properties of this new operation, +<sub>6</sub> that we've learned. First, notice that the number 0 behaves in a special way under +<sub>6</sub>. Whenever we combine 0 with anything else, we get that same thing back. We'll say that 0 is the <i>identity</i> under +<sub>6</sub>, because when you combine it with something it gives you that identical thing back.","rt":120730,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":42,"time_elapsed":931801,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"instructions":"Now that we know 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>, we're going to make a new definition. We'll s ay that  the <i>inverse</i> of a number is the thing that you combine with it to produce the identity. For example, 5 +<sub>6</sub> 1 = 0, so we say 1 is the inverse of 5 under +<sub>6</sub>, (remember 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>). Similarly, 3 is its own inverse under +<sub>6</sub>, because 3 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 0.","rt":3212,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":43,"time_elapsed":935021,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Now you try! What is the inverse of 4 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","response_history":["2"],"rt":5333,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":44,"time_elapsed":940356,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 4 under +<sub>6</sub> is 2 because 4 +<sub>6</sub> 2 = 0, and 0 is the identity unde r +<sub> 6</sub>.","rt":5722,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":45,"time_elapsed":946079,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 1 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"5","response":"3","response_history":["3"],"rt":3306,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":46,"time_elapsed":949387,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that was incorrect. The inverse of 1 under +<sub>6</sub> is 5 because 1 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":1483,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":47,"time_elapsed":950873,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 3 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce  the ide ntity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","response_history":["3"],"rt":2471,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":48,"time_elapsed":953345,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 3 under +<sub>6</sub> is 3 because 3 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":942,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":49,"time_elapsed":954289,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 2 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"4","response":"4","response_history":["4"],"rt":3006,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":50,"time_elapsed":957296,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 2 under +<sub>6</sub> is 4 becaus e 2 +<su b>6</sub> 4 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":1312,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":51,"time_elapsed":958609,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 0 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","response_history":["0"],"rt":2374,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":52,"time_elapsed":960984,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 0 under +<sub>6</sub> is 0 because 0 +<sub>6</sub> 0 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":863,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":53,"time_elapsed":961848,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"instructions":"It is also possible to successively apply +<sub>6</sub>, and the operation can simply be performed starting w ith the  left-most pair. For example, 2 +<sub>6</sub> 3 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 3.","rt":2574,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":54,"time_elapsed":964424,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"instructions":"We have one last definition to learn today, using the successive operations we just learned. Let's start with an example. Under our operation +<sub>6</sub> we can make every other number using just 1: 2 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, 3 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, 4 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, 5 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, and 0 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1. Because of this, we say that 1 is a <i>generator</i> under +<sub>6</sub>. <br /><br /> However, 2 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 4 = 2 +<sub>6</sub> 2, and 0 = 2 +<sub>6</sub> 2 +<sub>6</sub> 2, but there is no way to make 1, 3, or 5 using just 2.","rt":221556,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":55,"time_elapsed":1185981,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Now you try! Is 3 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"Yes","response_history":["Yes"],"rt":4061,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":56,"time_elapsed":1190050,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.9-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that's incorrect. 3 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 3 = 3, 0 = 3 +<sub>6</sub> 3, but there is no way to make 1, 2, 4, or 5 using just 3.","rt":1221,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":57,"time_elapsed":1191274,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.9-0"},{"question":"Is 5 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"Yes","response":"Yes","response_history":["Yes"],"rt":2142,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":58,"time_elapsed":1193418,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.9-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 5 is a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 5 = 5, 4 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, 3 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, 2 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, 1 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, and 0 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, so you can make all of the numbers under +<sub>6</sub> using 5","rt":1085,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":59,"time_elapsed":1194505,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.9-0"},{"question":"Is 4 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"Yes","response_history":["Yes"],"rt":2382,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":60,"time_elapsed":1196890,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.9-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that's incorrect. 4 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 4 = 4, 2 = 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4, and 0 = 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4, but there is no way to make 1, 3, or 5 using just 4.","rt":885,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":61,"time_elapsed":1197777,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.9-0"},{"question":"Is 0 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"No","response_history":["No"],"rt":1839,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":62,"time_elapsed":1199618,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.9-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 0 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 0 = 0, but there is no way to ma ke 1, 2,  3, 4, or 5 using just 0.","rt":829,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":63,"time_elapsed":1200449,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.9-0"},{"instructions":"Now we are going to ask you some questions about a new operation, +<sub>9</sub>, on the numbers 0, 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8. It works exactly like +<sub>6</sub>, except now after adding the two numbers you subtract 9 if your result is 9 or greater. <br /><br />We'll give you one practice question with feedback to make sure you understand the new operation. After that, try to complete the remaining questions as accurately as possible.","rt":1320,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":64,"time_elapsed":1201770,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Practice: What is 5 +<sub>9</sub> 5?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"1","response":"1","response_history":["1"],"rt":4028,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":65,"time_elapsed":1205800,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.11-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 5 +<sub>9</sub> 5 = 1 because 5 + 5 = 10 and 10 - 9 = 1.","rt":816,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":66,"time_elapsed":1206617,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.11-0"},{"question":"What is 3 +<sub>9</sub> 3?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"6","response":"6","response_history":["6"],"rt":4142,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":67,"time_elapsed":1210760,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.11-0"},{"question":"What is 7 +<sub>9</sub> 4?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","response_history":["2"],"rt":4286,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":68,"time_elapsed":1215047,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.11-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>9</sub> 8?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","response_history":["0"],"rt":2468,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":69,"time_elapsed":1217518,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.11-0"},{"question":"What is 5 +<sub>9</sub> 4?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","response_history":["0"],"rt":2816,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":70,"time_elapsed":1220335,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.11-0"},{"question":"What is 6 +<sub>9</sub> 6?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","response_history":["3"],"rt":2699,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":71,"time_elapsed":1223037,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.11-0"},{"question":"What is 4 +<sub>9</sub> 1? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"5 because 4+1 is 5 and 5 is less than 9","response_history":["5 because 4+1 is 5 and 5 is less than 9"],"rt":16253,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":72,"time_elapsed":1239292,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.11-0"},{"question":"What is 8 +<sub>9</sub> 4? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"3 because 8+4 is 12 and 12-9 is 3.","response_history":["3 because 8+4 is 12 and 12 minute","3 because 8+4 is 12 and 12 minut","3 because 8+4 is 12 and 12 minu","3 because 8+4 is 12 and 12 min","3 because 8+4 is 12 and 12 mi","3 because 8+4 is 12 and 12 m","3 because 8+4 is 12 and 12 ","3 because 8+4 is 12 and 12-9 is 3."],"rt":20347,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":73,"time_elapsed":1259640,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.11-0"},{"question":"What is the identity under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0. I don't know why, I'm just guessing.","response_history":["0. I don't know wy","0. I don't know why, I'm just guess.","0. I don't know why, I'm  just gu essing."],"rt":12997,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":74,"time_elapsed":1272638,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.11-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 5 under +<sub>9</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"4","response":"2","response_history":["2"],"rt":39682,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":75,"time_elapsed":1312321,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.11-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 2 under +<sub>9</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"7","response":"5","response_history":["5"],"rt":2433,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":76,"time_elapsed":1314755,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.11-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 3 under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"3","response_history":["3"],"rt":2277,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":77,"time_elapsed":1317033,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.11-0"},{"question":"Is 2 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"Yes because it has an inverse.","response_history":["No because that wouldn't make any sense.","Yes because it has an inverse."],"rt":16421,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":78,"time_elapsed":1333455,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.11-0"},{"question":"Is 3 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"No because it has no inverse.","response_history":["Yes because it has","No because it has no inverse."],"rt":32627,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":79,"time_elapsed":1366083,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.11-0"},{"question":"Is 5 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? P lease ex plain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"Yes because there is an inverse.","response_history":["Yes because there is an inverse."],"rt":39777,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":80,"time_elapsed":1405862,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.11-0"},{"question":"Is 6 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"Yes because there is an inverse.","response_history":["Yes because there is an inverse."],"rt":11996,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":81,"time_elapsed":1417859,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.11-0"},{"instructions":"Now we'd like to ask you some questions about +<sub>n</sub>, where n could be any postive counting number. For example, n could be 3, or n could be any other counting number you can think of. If you need to write the operation, you  can use  \"+_n\", and your answers can include n to stand in for the arbitrary value if necessary.","rt":5414,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":82,"time_elapsed":1423275,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"What is the formula for the inverse of 1 under +<sub>n</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"n-1","response":"I don't really know.","response_history":["I don't really know."],"rt":8094,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":83,"time_elapsed":1431370,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"What is the formula for the inverse of an element x under +<sub>n</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"n-x","response":"I honestly don't know, I get really confused when it comes to variables.","response_history":["I honestly don't know, I get really confused when it comes to variables."],"rt":15725,"trial_type":"qu estion","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":84,"time_elapsed":1447096,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"Is there a pattern to which elements are generators? How can you know if an element x is a generator under +<sub>n</sub> without seeing whether it can make all the elements?.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"I don't know.","response_history":["I don't know."],"rt":4806,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":85,"time_elapsed":1451903,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is an odd number, it must be a generator under +<sub>n</sub>.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["True","False"],"correct_response":"False","response":"True","response_history":["True"],"rt":4158,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":86,"time_elapsed":1456062,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is an even number, it must not be a generator under +< sub>n</s ub>.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["True","False"],"correct_response":"False","response":"True","response_history":["True"],"rt":1872,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":87,"time_elapsed":1457935,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is not a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, x must divide n.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["True","False"],"correct_response":"False","response":"False","response_history":["False"],"rt":1709,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":88,"time_elapsed":1459646,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is not a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, x must be a multiple of a divisor of n. Please explain in words why your answer is corret.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"True","response":"I don't know whether it's true or false.","response_history":["I don't know whether it's true or false."],"rt":10902,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":89,"time_elapsed":1470549,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"If an element x is a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, is its inverse a generator under +<sub>n</sub> always, sometimes, or never?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Always","Sometimes","Never"],"correct_response":"Always","response":"Sometimes","response_history":["Sometimes"],"rt":1925,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":90,"time_elapsed":1472477,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"if an element x is a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, is x +<sub>n</sub> x a generator under +<sub>n</sub> always, sometimes, or never? Please explain in words why your answer is corret.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"sometimes","response":"I really don't know.","response_history":["I really don't know."],"rt":6614,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":91,"time_elapsed":1479092,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"If an element x is not a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, is x +<sub>n</sub> x a generator under +<sub>n</sub> always, sometimes, or never?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Always","Sometimes","Never"],"correct_response":"Never","response":"Sometimes","response_history":["Sometimes"],"rt":2094,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":92,"time_elapsed":1481188,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"instructions":"We would like to ask you some questions about your background. Please press \"Continue\" to continue.","rt":1541,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":93,"time_elapsed":1482731,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"What is your age?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"22","response_history":["22"],"rt":1799,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":94,"time_elapsed":1484531,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"What is your level of education?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Did not graduate high school","High school diploma","Some college, no degree","Associates Degree","Bachelors Degree","Some graduate school, no degree","Masters Degree","Doctorate, M.D., etc."],"correct_response":"","response":"High school diploma","response_history":["High school diploma"],"rt":2159,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":95,"time_elapsed":1486691,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"What is the most advanced math class you've completed? If you have multiple classes and you're not sure which one is most advanced, please list them.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"Algebra 1","response_history":["Algebra 1"],"rt":6717,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":96,"time_elapsed":1493409,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"How familiar are you with the concept of modular arithmetic? ","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - never heard of it","2 - heard of it but didn't know what it was","3 - seen it used or explained","4 - used it but not often or recently","5 - used it, remember and understand it"],"correct_response":"1","response":"1 - never heard of it","response_history":["1 - never heard of it"],"rt":2960,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":97,"time_elapsed":1496370,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"How familiar are you with the concept of a mathematical group?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - never heard of it","2 - heard of it but didn't know what it was","3 - seen it used or explained","4 - used it but not often or recently","5 - used it, remember and understand it"],"correct_response":"1","response":"2 - heard of it but didn't know what it was","response_history":["2 - heard of it but didn't know what it was"],"rt":3005,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":98,"time_elapsed":1499376,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"Do you feel you learned something from this HIT?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - not at all","2 - somewhat","3 - definitely"],"correct_response":"1","response":"2 - somewhat","response_history":["2 - somewhat"],"rt":3023,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":99,"time_elapsed":1502401,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"Do you feel you understood the concepts in this HIT?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - not at all","2 - somewhat","3 - definitely"],"correct_response":"1","response":"1 - not at all","response_history":["1 - not at all"],"rt":2453,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":100,"time_elapsed":1504856,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"Did you enjoy this HIT?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - not at all","2 - somewhat","3 - definitely"],"correct_response":"1","response":"3 - definitely","response_history":["3  - definitely"],"rt":1934,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":101,"time_elapsed":1506791,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"What is your gender?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Female","Male","Other"],"correct_response":"","response":"Male","response_history":["Male"],"rt":2118,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":102,"time_elapsed":1508912,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"What is/are your native language(s)? (The languages spoken in your household when you were a child.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"English","response_history":["English"],"rt":4053,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":103,"time_elapsed":1512967,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"Did you use pen and paper at any point on this HIT?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"no","response_history":["no"],"rt":2478,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":104,"time_elapsed":1515446,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"Do you have any comments on this HIT?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"","response_history":[],"rt":1223,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":105,"time_elapsed":1516670,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"}]